[Episode 6]
["Many Advertising Offers for the New Couple"]
["Nation's Top Sweetheart Choi Yun"]
Nat...
Nat.. ion's... Top... Swee...
Mr. Cha!
Yun is washing up now.
Will you wait for him for a moment?
You have ketchup on your face.
No, not there.
Hold this. Let me see your face.
You're like a sloppy child with food on your face.
It's fine. When I meet my mother,
I'll have her wipe it off.
Managers represent their stars. You know that, right?
You become a reflection of Yun.
Your behavior, speech, clothing, manners.
Try not to tarnish Yun's image, okay?
Okay.
Also, have your clothes dry cleaned every day.
And don't go around eating these filthy things.
Oh. That's my Yun!
Excuse me.
Your picture came out gorgeous, son.
You're glamorous, son!
Choi Yun and Kang Minju shoot
many advertisements together...
Let's eat porridge, Yun.
I don't want to.
You'll be at the shoot all day.
You won't have any strength.
This was made with fresh abalone
from Jeju Island this morning.
Hurry, get up. You're a good son.
Ah!
Isn't it delicious?
No.
Let's give some to Muhyeok.
He probably hasn't eaten breakfast.
You're crazy.
There's only enough for you, and it's expensive.
It's too precious for me to eat, even.
It tastes funny.
Bro, can you go pick up Minju?
Minju's manager is ill.
Will you go get her?
Sure. No problem.
Hello.
Even a passing dog wouldn't be ignored like this.
Are you that special?
Who do you think you are anyway? What a joke.
Do you want to sleep with me?
If you get involved with me,
it'd be till death do us part.
If you haven't got the guts, don't even try.
Who on earth does he think he is?
Hey!
Hey, do you hear me?
This is the right car.
Hey, Mister Gangster!
That's for Yun! It's from his fans!
Don't eat anymore. It's Yun's!
If you want any, buy your own.
Move!
If you can't afford it, tear apart
the restaurant like you did before!
I said move!
No.
Why? You want to hit me, too?
Resort to violence one more time,
and that'll be the end of you.
I'll leave you and move to Africa!
Eunchae!
What's with you again? Why are you yelling at Muhyeok?
This is for you, but he keeps on eating it.
I won't eat it, then! Okay? So petty...
You're so petty. It's just food.
Let's eat!
You should eat slowly.
Are you okay?
Are you okay, Yun?
Now what are you up to?
Are you okay?
Action!
How's it coming along?
It's almost done.
How is it?
- Does it taste bad?
- Yeah.
What went wrong?
It's good!
- Really?
- Of course!
Ah, it's hot!
Let me see.
It burns.
Wait a moment. I got something in my eye.
Yun!
Move your hand.
What is it? It feels big.
- Are you okay?
- No. I'm not okay.
Stupid blockhead!
Why did you do that?
He has Minju. Are you stupid?
Stupid blockhead. Stupid stupid...
You'll dent the car, blockhead.
That's too much.
Bigger.
You think that'll come out?
- No...
- Alright, alright. Write it quick.
Hey! You guys.
Tell me your school, grade, and names.
You're all dead.
Do you know how harmful rumors are?
You with the red scarf! Give me your name first.
Who the heck are you? So what's your name?
You think this is a game?
You guys. You seem to be Yun's fans
Are these the actions of true fans?
Yeah!
If you really love Yun, then you
should love the person Yun loves.
No way!
If you really care about Yun...
That's enough.
You little...
You're pathetic. Get out of my face.
What a loser!
Why you...
No! You get out of my face, you brats!
Yun wouldn't thank fans like you.
What?
Step on her.
Do you want to die?
Good job, Mister.
You listened well and you're much nicer.
No matter what happens, just stay out of it.
I get beat up by someone once every two months anyway.
Even if I, the girl of your dreams,
gets a little hurt, keep your cool.
Got it?
Violence is bad, regardless.
With how strong you are, you'd have killed them!
Kang... Min... Ju.
Chea... ter...
Don't read it aloud. It's nonsense.
It's so pathetic.
Celebrities can't love anyone
without having a hard time.
Why isn't this coming off?
I have to erase it all before Yun comes.
Grandfather...
Stop it.
Stop crying and eat with me.
You want me to mix that in?
You're here.
My sister... Where is she?
In the bathroom. She's washing up.
Galchi, did you call your uncle?
Bad people hit my... my mom!
And kissed and stuff when she told them no!
It seems that two thugs were
playing a joke on Seo-kyeong.
The police came to help before
anything really happened.
She's probably in shock, but she's okay.
It happens every now and again.
Nothing for you to worry about.
Why did you call your uncle? You probably worried him.
If you haven't eaten yet, sit down and eat with us.
Galchi, sit down. It's delicious. Sit!
Come here.
Sit, sit down.
Such a temper.
Galchi, have some. It's delicious.
Seo-kyeong!
Do you... Do you want my help?
If you use this...
It hurts, doesn't it?
I'm sorry.
About before... For yelling at you
and screaming at you.
I'm sorry.
I won't do it again. I'm sorry.
You're so pretty, my sister.
I didn't know how pretty you were.
I'll wash it all away for you.
Those guys...
Where... Where did they kiss you?
Over here?
And?
Here.
I'll wash it clean.
I'll wash it all away for you.
Mom...
It's so funny!
Eunchae.
Song Eunchae!
Oh, Dad.
Do you want to have a drink with me?
Sure.
But we don't have any soju. I'll go and buy some now.
I get 5 points!
Yes!
Oh my, I got so unlucky!
You can have it.
Blockhead.
Mister?
Why are you here at this time?
Give me...
Give me a hug.
Huh?
Like with Yun. Just one hug.
Have you been drinking?
Hug me, just once.
Get up and go home.
It's cold. You'll catch a cold.
Mister!
Mister Pervert!
Mister Gangster!
Hello.
Choi Yun.
Excuse me. Do you have any sweet buns?
Hey, Minchae! Isn't this your sister?
Here!
Eunchae! Eunchae!
Choi Yun and his coordinator, Song, appear to have been
romantically involved since before Choi Yun's debut.
Choi Yun, who has been dating scandal queen Minju,
was previously hailed as
Korea's good and honest sweetheart,
but he now shows his true colors.
The news of Ms. Song and Yun, high school friends,
is shocking to all.
Goodness! I knew this day would come.
Since it's in the open, are you guys really friends?
People would sooner guess
you two were a married couple!
That's what I'm saying.
Even if she doesn't know her friends' phone numbers,
she probably has all of Yun's
friends' phone numbers memorized.
That's what I'm saying!
If I told her to pick out his
underpants from a line up of ten,
Eunchae could do it.
Not even Yun's mother would know, but she would.
That's what I'm saying.
Eunchae's bra size, underwear size, shoe size.
I don't even know them but Yun knows!
That's what I'm saying!
You people are no help at all.
So what's your point? That the news article is true?
No! Not that! What we're saying is...
What are we saying?
Well. You were blabbing. I didn't say much.
Who is it?
Who took those absurd photos?
Who is attacking my son like this?
Whoever he is, bring him to me!
Find him, wherever he is.
Calm down, ma'am.
How can I stay calm?
This is ruining my Yun's image.
Three commercials have been cancelled.
We'll have to pay the contract violation damages
in the lipstick ad too!
My heart is racing.
Should I get you some medicine?
You started this and now you try to help?
I mean, is Eunchae out of her mind?
Yun is soft-hearted. There's nothing we can do
about him, but she should've been careful!
I apologize.
What would people think of Yun?
That he's a perverted Casanova who's
on and off with his friend?
Why Eunchae of all people?
Yun's of a whole different class!
What do you mean by that?
What?
She's a coordinator, so what?
Is a star so special?
Do celebrities fall from heaven?
The way I see it, they're all the same.
Hey.
Eunchae does have strength.
She's 100 times stronger than your son.
Are you out of your mind?
I can endure anything, but I won't
let you insult my daughter!
So hold your tongue, you brat!
Yun!
Where are you going?
Yun...
Minju.
Recipient did not answer.
Where are you, Yun?
Minju.
Sweet potato.
[Sweet potado]
Don't cheat!
I'm not.
Let's see.
Both of you are pretty stupid.
After all I've taught,
you still can't spell "sweet potato"?
It's so easy! Sweet potato.
Well, that's what I wrote.
How is that sweet potato?
This is how you spell it.
Another one then.
Potato.
[Korea's Sweetheart Choi Yun Has Haters For First Time]
[Ad deals canceled over blow to image]
"Yun's agency has not released any official statement.
Rumors about Choi Yun and the Song family
are leaking constantly.
The two are still living in the same house."
What's going to happen to Yun?
If I were Eunchae, I'd hold onto him really tight.
How do you function with a brain like that?
Do you want to live like this?
Yes. This is the way I live.
What are you going to do about it?
Just because you're tall.
Let's go to the market. Buy me steamed bread, sister.
- You don't have money?
- No... Let's go.
- Hi.
I've experienced it before, so I know.
It's nothing for you to cry over.
Gosh!
So why do something that'd cause a scandal?
You two are too close even in my eyes.
It's more than close.
You took off your underwear in front of her, right?
Shouldn't she have been more careful?
You have a girlfriend now. She should act accordingly.
I told Eunchae to keep her distance
from you for a while.
I know a good coordinator.
Do you want to have someone take her place?
All right. I won't do that.
Eunchae!
Our Yun has been up since morning
and has been crying for four hours now.
What can we do? He'll probably die if we let him.
I feel like dying myself.
You go and try to comfort Yun.
Oh, what a loser. You cry just because of some news?
You're like a baby. Should I bring your bottle, baby?
This would have been a good headline.
"Popular singer Choi Yun is the biggest baby ever!"
What are you staring at?
If it weren't true, you wouldn't be like this.
The fact that you love Minju is obvious to everyone.
And you and I being friends only, God and Buddha know.
Even with those shoots canceled,
you can still make a living.
Is it about your image?
I'll go to reporters and clear things up.
- Who says it's because of that?
- Then what?
Minju won't look at me.
It'd be great if she even got a little angry
but she's not even angry.
I was at Minju's house for ten hours.
All she did was play video games.
She didn't even look at me once.
Minju and I've come this far.
What will I do if Minju dumps me?
Then I'm going to kill myself.
I'm going to kill myself then.
Die...
Then just die.
Go upstairs... Yun isn't crying anymore.
Where's Yun?
You must not have heard. His shoot was cancelled today.
Did the assistant call you?
Then you can leave.
Isn't that Song Eunchae?
Are you Song Eunchae? Please let us interview you.
Are the news reports about your relationship true?
What was your first thought? Reaction?
What is this?
Put that away! Go!
How do you feel right now?
- Go!
- Song Eunchae, will you tell us your thoughts?
Song Eunchae! Song Eunchae!
Wait! One moment.
If you put away the cameras,
I'll give you an interview.
Yun and I were born in the same house
and for 25 years we'd been friends.
We were breastfed by the same mother
and raised like twins.
My father is Yun's mother's chauffer.
And my mother is their maid.
My family rents out the basement room of Yun's house.
If I had ever had feelings for Yun,
I would have been too ashamed to
live under such conditions,
and would have moved out.
I'm sure Yun feels the same way.
Even if only for a moment,
if he ever had feelings for me,
he wouldn't tell me how much he loves Minju,
how his life is precious because of her,
or how he wants to die because of her.
He couldn't have told those things to me.
Are there any other questions you'd like to ask?
Start the music!
Yun is the one I stabbed.
So why are you the one bleeding? Blockhead.
Go.
Why'd you come here? Go.
Minju!
I told you not to find me.
I told you not to find me!
Minju!
Before people see this, leave. Leave now!
Minju... Please...
Mom, Dad will kill both of us! Don't you know that?
I won't come again.
I won't come again, so...
So have dinner with me once.
I have a room at the Seoul hotel, so come there.
If you're scared of your father, then come there.
Listen carefully.
My relationship with you ended
when you took Dad away from me. It was over then.
Don't be so pathetic. Go.
Minju!
Go, go, Mom!
I'm not your daughter anymore!
Minju...
Do you need help?
I lost my car keys...
Where do you want to go?
I warned you, didn't I?
That if you lack the confidence,
you shouldn't mess with me.
If you get involved with me,
it'd be till death do us part.
Didn't I say that?
So then... Why approach me?
Minju...
[Episode 7 Preview]
I don't think I'll ever find someone who'll
like me as much as he does.
Blockhead! Blockhead!
[Sorry, if she is mine]
Well, you are nice.
You learned Korean. You like kimchi.
I'm so proud of you, mister.
[Love, I'll just stop everything here]
You've never put on lotion before?
Warm, fresh seaweed rolls for sale!